http://www.sjgames.com/general/privacy.html

SJ Games Privacy Policy
Last modified on May 24, 2018.
This Privacy Policy explains how we use any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect about you. This Privacy Policy applies to visitors to warehouse23.com and sjgames.com, and it also applies to our registered users. By visiting or using these sites, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Please do not use this site if you do not agree to these terms and conditions.
What does the Privacy Policy cover?
This Privacy Policy covers the warehouse23.com and sjgames.com websites, and it is limited to information collected while on these websites. It does not cover websites other than those listed in this Privacy Policy, and it does not apply to information collected by Steve Jackson Games through any other means.
The terms of the Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable laws.
What Personal Information do we collect? How do we use it?
During the course of a transaction or email-based interaction with Steve Jackson Games, you may be asked to submit several pieces of Personal Information, including full name, address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and expiration date. This information is solicited solely for the purposes of facilitating and communicating with you about that specific transaction or email topic. You don't have to provide us with Personal Information to access our websites, but some website features may not be available to you if you choose not to provide us with Personal Information. We will use that information for as long as required to complete the transaction or address the topic of your communication with us, unless laws or regulations mandate a longer period of time.
Some common activities that might have us request or collect information from you on a voluntary basis include the following:
You create an account on our forums or on Warehouse 23.
You make a purchase on Warehouse 23.
You send us an email with a question or concern.
You enter a shipping or billing address when making a purchase on Warehouse 23.
You sign up for a mailing list on our sites.
Transactions
For Warehouse 23, the transaction is a single order.
For subscriptions, the transaction is for the duration of the subscription.
For forums, the information gathered does not have a transaction limitation, and that information is used only to allow you to continue to access the website forums.
For emails, we will remain in contact with you for the duration of the discussion about the topic you emailed us about.
Credit Cards, PayPal, and Auctions
At Warehouse 23, we use an automated, "blind" credit card processing system; we do not ever see your full credit card number or the expiration date. You will have the option to store your credit card information when you create an account.
We also provide an option to pay for transactions using PayPal. When you use PayPal's website to make a payment to us, you are subject to PayPal's Privacy Policy, which you can review on their Privacy Policy page.
We use eBay to auction off older items that we have found deep in the warehouse. When you use eBay's website to bid on one of our items, you are subject to their Privacy Policy, not ours. Please see eBay's policies for more information.
Email Addresses and Warehouse 23
Email addresses, along with first and last name, are kept on file in order to notify customers when updated versions of purchased products become available.
Message Boards, Mailing Lists, and Forums
This Privacy Policy does not cover information voluntarily submitted and displayed on the message boards, sent to mailing lists, or posted in forums.
IP Addresses
As part of our efforts to prevent fraudulent transactions, we log your IP address when you place an order. If we determine that a transaction is fraudulent, we will report it to the appropriate authorities.
Cookies
This site uses cookies for a better shopping and browsing experience. Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you're viewing that website. To have a smoother and more enjoyable website visit, please enable cookies in your browser settings before shopping.
External Links and External Sites
When you click on a link that leads you to another website, you are subject to the external site's Privacy Policy and our Privacy Policy no longer applies. For example, if you wish to pay for a Warehouse 23 transaction using PayPal, you will be subject to PayPal's Privacy Policy while on their site, not ours. Also, if you're sharing a Warehouse 23 link on Facebook, you are subject to Facebook's Privacy Policy during the process of sharing that link. We recommend that you read the external site's Privacy Policy before submitting any information to that website.
Children and COPPA Compliance
To comply with COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), no one under the age of 13 may create an account on our sites or sign up for a mailing list. Teenagers of ages 13-17 may use the websites, and we may collect Personal Information from them if they submit it. We also may ask for a parent's or guardian's email address so that we can inform the parent or guardian about the teenager's activities. All information submitted by a teenager is treated in accordance with our Privacy Policy. To read more about COPPA, visit the COPPA website. To learn how to provide your children with a safe and enjoyable online experience, we recommend that you visit the ESRB website and read their advice for online safety.
Business Communication
In the course of operating our business, we receive resumes, charity requests, and other business-oriented communications. These are classified as being a business information relationship and we treat those differently (and thus these communications are not subject to this Privacy Policy).
What rights do California residents have?
According to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, users of our websites who are residents of California can request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you have questions about how your information has been shared, please contact us:
Steve Jackson Games
P.O. Box 18957
Austin, TX 78760
What rights do EU citizens have?
EU citizens have the right to access, change, and erase their personal information.
They may request that their stored personal information be provided to them, or be removed from our systems.
We may collect your personal information with your consent, which can be revoked.
We also may collect your personal information for our legitimate interests, including improving the presentation, operation, and experience of our services, evaluating and updating our technical infrastructure, and monitoring and improving the security of our sites.
We may also collect personal information for the purpose of processing payments and delivering products to you.
If you wish to change your personal information, you may do so from within your Account settings in Warehouse 23, from within your User Settings on the forums, from the Preferences link in our marketing mailing lists, or by contacting us at info@sjgames.com.
If you wish to request that your stored personal information be provided to you or removed from our systems, please contact info@sjgames.com. (Please bear in mind that we are a small company with diverse systems and limited resources.
This will be a manual process that will take some time.)
Do you have questions about this Privacy Policy?
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us and ask! We hope that your experience on our sites is delightful and fun, and we appreciate any feedback you can provide.
Top of Page | Home | Privacy Policy | Contact Us
